You could even win a reward!
We're on our way, racing towards
the village at breakneck speed.
Between Shimei Lai using his wind
magic to make the wagon hover,
and Lammis and Director Bear
pushing with all their might,
we might get there way
sooner than expected.
And so round two begins.
Struggle against me with all
your might, you will not lord me!
Give your lives and
your power to my cause!
We've got to get back fast and
stop him from getting his way!
On the outside, I'm just a big metal box,
but inside, I've still got a human soul!
In this new world of wonders,
I travel to and fro on the back
of my super strong partner,
Lamas!
The name's Boxo. Hello there!
That means yes, by the way.
I'll
see
you
next
time.
It didn't take us long at all to
get back to the transfer circle.
Thanks to Lamas and Director
Bear running non-stop.
Meanwhile, Captain Kerioyl and the school
director went back to the Origin Stratum.
Director!
Rector!
The trouble started while you were away.
I'm so sorry.
Give me all the details.
Yes, sir.
A few days ago, a swarm of
monsters came out of nowhere.
We tried, but we weren't able to
stop them from invading the village.
Most of the residents unfortunately
couldn't get inside in time.
I know this is difficult, but
you must tell me everything.
It's imperative that I hear
even the smallest piece,
so we know exactly where we stand.
Yes, sir.
We tried to activate the transfer circle,
but it wouldn't work for some reason.
Please tell me these aren't
the only survivors. No, sir.
There are more upstairs in private rooms.
The mothers with very young children,
the badly wounded, and more.
Then there are the hunters, too.
We have them on guard duty
on the second floor terrace.
I see.
You've done well, comrade.
Now get some rest.
We can...
Director!
We'll go help with guard
duty on the terrace.
We can better assess the situation
from up there too as gate guardians.
That's our job.
I'll assist in defending the town
I'm coming too.
I may have old man magic, but it
always comes through in a pinch
Watch out old lady on your heels.
Someone up there is sure to need some
healing I want to help you guys with defense.
No Lamas and Boxer.
We need your help with meal distribution
It doesn't seem like anybody's
been eating all that much.
Hello there.
Oh
Okay, poor Lamas.
I bet she's worried sick and wants
to find Munami, her pal from the inn.
If she went in a battle with
that weighing on her mind,
she'd probably just mess things up.
Whoa, what's going on?
Is Boxo doing all this?
Wow, this water is so cold and tasty!
It is so delicious too!
Thanks so much, Boxo.
The resilience of these people
never ceases to amaze me.
Makes me want to do my
vending machine best!
All right, Boxo, on to the second floor!
Hey, everybody!
Cold drinks and hot food!
Come and get it!
Hello!
We've got food and drinks out here.
It's the big strong lady!
Are Grandma and Grandpa with you?
Mm-hmm.
Yumite and Shimelai
are both safe and well.
Don't worry.
They're okay!
I'm so happy!
Lamas!
Hey, look who I found!
Yumite and Shimalai's
daughter and granddaughter.
And they're both safe.
Amazing.
Karyos' girlfriend, the
exchange house gang,
and that domineering blonde
girl, they're all safe.
Oh, also... Mommy!
I've never been so happy
to see you! Munami!
Thank goodness! I missed you!
Boxxo, I want to let the elderly
fighters know their girls are safe.
Could you help me out?
How about that?
Okay. Form change!
Nice.
I appreciate you, Voxo.
No, this can't be.
Look at what those monsters have
done to our precious village.
You and me, I'm devastated too.
But right now, we've got
important work at hand.
Who knew Shirley and
Goat Guy were so strong?
A gobsmacked!
Hey, old-timers!
Your daughter and granddaughter are safe!
And Karios, your girl is too! Aye!
Boring strike!
Everyone's doing everything they can.
I can't let them show me up.
Is everyone all right?
Boxer, are you okay?
Are all your parts working
and in the right place?
Hello there.
Yulami, you two?
Looks like Lamas is feeling better.
The only safe place for
you to rest is inside.
I'll take care of things from here.
All right, it's fighting time.
I guess seeing Moon in me
really boosted her morale.
Hey, Lamas, nice to see you.
Sure, good to see you.
Wow, I love that outfit.
Thank you so much.
Had to come take a quick break.
Hold up there.
Whoa, how did you, uh, was
that your magic, Lamas?
Nope, that was courtesy of Boxo. Really?
Boxo did this?
Well then, thank you.
You seem like a top-notch guy.
Too bad you're a magic item.
Wow.
If I weren't a box, I
might get the wrong idea.
Right.
Time for Boxo and me to hold the line.
You go take a long nap, okay, Shirley?
You always say lack of sleep
is the arch-enemy of beauty.
Dang, I feel called
out, but I can't argue.
Okay, time to slay some monsters.
Incredible, Lumet.
I would love to transform into a power
washer and help everyone out there,
but I'd better keep that one in
my back pocket for time's sake.
The defensive wall's been breached?
Is that how the monsters are getting in?
Hey, Boxxo, may I have some water?
Lammis, are you tired
out already? Oh, right.
She ran all the way home
without stopping to rest.
Of course she's exhausted.
Right, ready for round two.
All thanks to you, Boxo.
And you too, Lamas. Let's go!
Get ready!
Yeah, me too.
Too bad, too bad.
You're pushing too hard.
You've got to rest, Lamas.
No, Boxo.
I want to keep going to save them.
I won't run.
I'll fight till the end.
I can protect everyone.
It won't be like when I was small.
Oh, Lamas.
Long ago, our village was attacked,
wiped out by a horde of monsters.
Few survived, but Lamas and I
were among the ones who did.
Our parents, though,
they weren't so lucky.
This is bringing Lamas back to
when her old village was destroyed.
I can understand the feeling, but if she
keeps pushing this hard, she could die.
Okay.
I have to stop her.
Now's my chance to try
what I've been practicing.
No time like the present!
Here goes nothing!
Lammis.
Stay back.
Oh, yeah.
I should maybe stay back, huh?
But, uh...
Bokshu!
Did you just say my name? You did!
Didn't you, Bokshu?
When did you learn to talk?
Llamas was so shocked that I spoke,
she screamed her head off
and then promptly passed out.
Guess that development really pushed
her mind and body over the edge.
Rest up, Llamas.
Hey, Boxo.
Did I just hear Llamas
yelling what I think I did?
Something about how you could talk? Yes.
Wait, what? Really?
Only a bit.
Oh, so that means what?
That you can talk a bit,
just not quite fluently?
Yes.
So that halting way you're speaking,
is it because there are limits to
what syllables you have to draw from?
It really is helpful that
she's so quick on the uptake.
Hello there.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to serving you again.
You could even win a reward.
Too bad.
You win.
Please insert coins.
I get it.
You can take parts of
the words you use in your
stock phrases and create
new words from them.
Yes, yes.
You're only saying a few sounds at a time.
Is that all you can manage?
K-lo-s-ba-it-ni-ot-k-wo-ite.
When I say sections of my
canned phrases, it sounds fine.
But when I string individual
syllables together,
it always ends up sounding
like an old-school robot voice.
I understand.
Or I think I do, for the most part.
That's incredible, though, Boxo.
Now you can communicate
much better than before.
I know that Lamas is
going to be over the moon.
I mean, I'm over the moon, too, obviously.
There's so much to learn.
I want to know everything about you.
It must feel so awkward for her to
say such un-Hula-me-like things.
While I would love to sit and enjoy
this conversation, now is not the time.
You want to go back out to
the terrace? You got it.
I don't ever get tired, so I'm the
best guy for tests of endurance?
because I'm a vending machine!
I can't stay transformed longer than
the time limit, but I can still do this!
That old favorite, cola and mint candy.
Cola Bombs!
how's that cola spray
feels great in those big
dumb monster eyes there's
more where that came from
boxo apparently the monster horde
typically retreats in the early
evening so they can launch a fierce
late night attack that means we had to
put up a late night defense there
was unanimous agreement not to ask
too much of our elderly hunters
director bear hadn't gotten any sleep.
So he's zonked out on Hulumi's super
strong homemade sleep medicine.
Heads up, comrades.
Four creatures incoming,
and they're moving quickly.
Guess who's back?
Oh, looks like everyone else is back, too.
It's Boxo.
Give us something real tasty
to eat right now, Boxo.
I'm glad to see the band of gluttons
demanding food before celebrating our reunion.
means they're feeling like themselves.
Behold, your favorite fried chicken!
We looked!
All around!
Save it for when you're
done eating, Mikenne.
Where was I?
Oh, right, so we ran around the village
looking for survivors of the attack.
But no matter where we
went, we couldn't find any.
And as far as the monsters, they're
gathered together near a big hole?
they made in the wall.
And more and more keep showing up.
We saw several big ones way off
in the distance headed this way.
Wow, these little guys were
running around in this danger zone?
Which means it's reasonable
to assume we can expect the
King Frog Fiends to show up
tomorrow or the day after.
Comrades, we must focus
on the task before us.
And while there isn't much I can
do, I swear I'll give it my all.
With our combined strength, I know we
can dispose of these Fel Fiends handily.
Wow, he nailed that speech.
He's really charming when
he goes into manly mode.
Now, if he could just do
something about that trembling,
clenched fist, he'd be golden.
Mishuel's trying his best,
despite his awkward ways.
You heard the man.
No taking reckless risks.
If you get hurt, get
back inside immediately.
Reinforcement hunters and
the healing squad will
be waiting right on the
other side of the door.
Great job, apprentice.
Now just relax and have
a nice chocolate drink.
Oh, uh, thanks, Master.
I'm so grateful.
Boxxo, we'll protect everyone.
We can't afford to lose anyone else.
And I have a plan, assuming the ecology
here is anything like it is on Earth.
The real question is
whether she'll let me.
Yes, what is it, Boxxo?
What, you want me to put
you down there? No way!
A bunch of enemies are on
their way here right now!
Well, I don't care!
It's way too dangerous!
I refuse to let you do it!
Doesn't look like anything
I say will convince her.
In which case...
All right, eh, please.
How come you haven't
said my name yet, Boxo?
Huh, what, is she pouting?
I have almost all the
sounds, everything but the M.
That's fine for Llamas, but would
Hulemy sound too weird without the M?
Great, I can see it on her face.
She knows my limitations
and she's testing me.
I can play your game.
You are cute.
What?
Well, that came right
out of nowhere, Boxo.
Don't think you can weasel
your way out I'm proud
of saying my name with
such flagrant flattery.
Heh, I win this round.
So, Boxo, are you actually
flirting with Hulemy? Oh, no.
Lamas is pouting?
This is bad. Lamas?
It looks like Boxo's cooked up a strategy.
Why don't we let him try it? Huh?
That means go while I still can.
Thanks, Hulemy.
Form change!
We've got just under
an hour till midnight,
and I have over an hour left
where I can be transformed.
That means if I start now, I've got
just enough time as a different model.
Current point total is...
A hundred thousand.
It went way down from
fighting the Netherlord,
but now I have plenty
thanks to Director Bear who
inserted a bunch of gold coins
as advance payment earlier.
Form change!
What's that thing?
Hey, that's Voxo, isn't it?
I think you're shooting ice!
And look how much there is!
Most of the enemies are snake,
frog, and crocodile monsters.
On Earth, they'd be cold-blooded animals.
They should have trouble
with extreme heat or cold.
I'll surround the association with ice,
which will lower the
temperature dramatically.
Here they come i can't
tell if the ice is working
but now that i've up
to my stats i should be
able To do more with
the existing ice got to
concentrate bring the ice
together and harden it
Started spinning and then rocketed
beyond the barrier bombs away
Awesome it worked now.
I've just got to keep
There's no sneaking up on a vending
machine with a 360 degree field of vision.
I'm taking all of you out Right now!
Hey, Boss No!
Is Shulami talking to me?
Your abilities consume money as
their primary energy source, right?
Should you really be
using them so liberally?
What are you worried about?
Director Bear paid me ten
gold coins in advance!
What the heck?
What is happening?
I had 100,000 points left!
Is it super expensive to launch
things using the barrier or something?
I honestly have no idea!
But I do know I had better hightail it.
I'm back!
How am I gonna get out of this one?
You sit there and think
about what you've done.
Welp, I am a vending machine, so sitting
here is definitely in my wheelhouse?
but I'd do it all again.
I thought I told you I didn't
want you to go down there!
Why would you just ignore me, huh?
Don't get me wrong, I believe
in you wholeheartedly.
But still, if you asked me not to
do something and I did it anyway...
At times like this, it's best to
just be quiet and look real sorry.
Oh, I see.
You think if you sit there quietly looking
real sorry, I'll forgive and forget?
Hello there.
I do like that she can read
me, but sometimes it's scary.
The way my points were draining so fast
in giant vending machine mode was scary,
too.
I was not expecting that at all.
Are you even listening to me?
I've had it up to here, Boxo.
I know Lamas is just mad because
she cares and was worried about me,
but I hope she gets it
out of her system soon.
I think we're safe for tonight,
but tomorrow it starts again.
I know things would be
much easier if we could
do something about that
breach in the wall.
I guess all I can do right now is help
everyone sleep soundly by diffusing a nice,
relaxing floral scent.
This frozen treat is terrific.
So sweet and refreshing. You said it.
I don't think I've ever had anything
this cold and yummy in my whole life.
Hey, let's have a bite of each other's.
Oh, you bet.
I thought you'd never ask.
I thought the ice cream would
help everyone beat the heat.
And it's great to see
how much they love it.
It is time for the War
Council to commence.
The first order of business is closing
off the gap in the protective wall.
Without that, we're
just chasing our tails.
Does anyone have ideas?
Yulami.
There's a ton of rubble at the site
of the breach in the wall, right?
Moving that's going to be our best option.
The question then becomes how
many here can manipulate Earth.
Let me think for a moment.
I believe three people.
And then there's Shimei.
Earth magic, huh?
Not my specialty, but I
can still give it a go.
We can figure something out.
Just gotta summon enough
earth magic to cover the gap.
I have an idea.
Couldn't Boxxo turn into that big thing
from last night and fill the hole?
I look forward to serving you again.
Yeah, that's actually not a bad idea.
The problem is that
Boxxo uses exponentially
more money when he
changes into other forms.
That one?
It takes even more than his smaller forms.
I bet something that large
would require quite the sum.
Thanks for always having my back, Yulami.
You have to f' you coins?
Only for a bit!
It means you can do it for a little while.
But maintaining it for a
long time is more difficult.
If you could buy us some time at least?
Then the rest of us can work
quickly to repair the breach point.
How much more coin does the Hunters
Association have in reserve?
About 60 gold as far as I
know Wow, that little you say
Boxo,
how long do you suppose you could maintain
that form if we gave you 60 gold coins 60
coins that equals 60 000 points but i was
shocked at how quickly i
burned through them last
night director bear
suori if it's money you
need then i might have
a brilliant idea that
could save the whole town
suori have you really
got a plan to get us
out of this Christmas?
Thank you.
You could even win a reward.
I look forward to serving you again.